<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LASU STAFF CORNER</string>

    <string name="lasustaff_string">LASU STAFF</string>
    <string name="corner_string">CORNER</string>
    <string name="great_lasu_string">Professor I.I.Olatunji-Bello mni, fnli, NPOM</string>
    <string name="hurrah_string">welcomes you!</string>

    <string name="get_started">Get Started</string>
    <string name="btn_signin">SIGN IN</string>
    <string name="btn_signup">SIGN UP</string>

    <string name="lasu_law">LASU LAW</string>

    <string name="hint_password"><font size="50">........</font></string>
    <string name="hint_email"><font size="15">oluwatoyin.enikuomehin@lasu.edu.ng</font></string>
    <string name="hint_username"><font size="15">OluwatoyinEni</font></string>
    <string name="txt_signin">Sign in</string>
    <string name="txt_signup">Sign up</string>

    <string name="getting_started">Getting Started</string>
    <string name="create_acct">Create an account to continue</string>
    <string name="agree">By creating an account, you agree to our</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_acct">Already have an account?</string>

    <string name="txt_lasu_law">LASU LAW</string>
    <string name="txt_cos">Condition of Service</string>
    <string name="txt_fp">Financial Policy</string>
    <string name="txt_pg">Promotion Guildlines</string>
    <string name="txt_exam">Exam Policy</string>
    <string name="txt_lasg">LASG Public Service</string>
    <string name="txt_faculty">Faculty and Departments</string>
    <string name="txt_council">Governing Council and Management Staff</string>
    <string name="txt_constitution">Nigerian Constitution</string>
    <string name="txt_act">Procurement Act</string>
    <string name="txt_info">LASU INFO</string>
    <string name="txt_ict">ICT Releases</string>

    <string name="vc_welcome_address">
        <![CDATA[<p>It is my distinct honor and privilege to welcome you to the LASU STAFF CORNER, the official Staff APP of our esteemed University. As the Vice Chancellor, I am delighted to extend my warmest greetings to all those who have embarked upon this journey of knowledge, discovery, and endless possibilities with us.</p>
        <br><p>This APP serves as a virtual gateway to our vibrant academic community, offering a window into the heart and soul of our institution. Here, you will find information and resources that embody our policies and operational principles as approved by Law and as entrenched in our commitment to excellence in education, research, and community engagement.</p>
        <br><p>As you navigate through these digital pages, you will uncover a wealth of knowledge that embodies the foundation of our University, the State, and the Country at large. From the LAW establishing the University to the Condition of Service for both Senior and Junior Staff members, we have covered a range of resources that give us a better footage as staff members of the University.</p>
        <br><p>In this CORNER, you will also be able to report issues around you even as you get regular updates from the University.</p>
        <br><p>This solution further encapsulates the essence of our university\'s pursuit of intellectual growth, openness, and innovation.</p>
        <br><p>As we embark on this digital journey together, I encourage each and every one of you to actively engage with the LASU CORNER, get updates, and contribute to its growth.</p>
        <br><p>Welcome to our university\'s digital world, where possibilities know no bounds.</p>
        <br><p>We are LASU, we are great.</p>
        <br><b>Prof. Ibiyemi I. Olatunji-Bello mni, fnli, NPOM</b>
        <p>Vice Chancellor</p><br><br><br><br>.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="abt_text_constitution_of_nigeria">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>1999 CONSTITUTION OF THE FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF NIGERIA</b>
        <br><p>In Nigeria, the 1999 constitution supersedes all other laws, including State laws passed by the House of Assembly and Acts of the National Assembly. It is the supreme law in the nation through which all other laws derive theirs power, legitimacy and must submit to. The law is binding on all citizens of the nation and serves as a legal compass for institutional and individual behaviour within the country.</p>
        <p>The 1999 constitution makes provision for economic policy, political objectives, social objectives, foreign policy objectives, educational objectives, environmental objectives, guidelines for Nigerian culture, obligation of the Mass media, National ethics, rights and duties of citizen. It is expected that the contents of the constitution will instill some measure of accountability and discipline in the conduct of political leaders.</p>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="abt_text_cos">
        <![CDATA[
        <p>The Lagos State University Conditions of Service contains rules, rights, requirements, and policies that govern the relationship between the University and its staff. It is a document that guides the conduct of staff and prescribes the responsibilities of the staff to the University and vice versa.</p>

        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="text_cos_senior_chapter_one">
        <![CDATA[

        <head>
                <h1>CHAPTER ONE</h1>
        </head>

            <body>
                <h2>PREAMBLE</h2>
                <p><strong>1.1 TITLE:</strong></p>
                <p>These Regulations may be cited as the Regulations Guiding the Service of Senior Staff of the Lagos State University (LASU).</p>

                <p><strong>1.2 APPLICATION:</strong></p>
                <p>These Regulations shall apply in respect of any office or employment in any College, School, Faculty, Division, Department, Unit, or in any service center however designated, which is a part of the Lagos State University.</p>

                <p><strong>1.3 INTERPRETATION:</strong></p>
                <p>a) i. In the event of any question or doubt arising out of, or in connection with these Regulations, the matter, except on financial issues, shall be referred in the first instance to the Registrar for clarification, interpretation or decision, and thence on an appeal to the Vice-Chancellor whose decision shall supersede previous decision.<br> ii. In respect of financial matters, the matter shall in the first instance, be referred to the Bursar for clarification, interpretation or decision, and thence on an appeal to the Vice-Chancellor whose decision shall supersede previous decision.</br></p>
                <p>b) Where a staff member is of the view that the interpretation of the Vice-Chancellor is prejudicial to him/her so far as his/her terms and Conditions of Service are concerned, he may appeal to the Council against the decision of the Vice-Chancellor and the decision of the Council shall be final.</p>

                <p><strong>1.4 DEFINITIONS:</strong></p>
                <p>In these Regulations, unless the context otherwise requires or permits, the following expressions shall have the following meanings:</p>
                <ol>
                    <li><strong>Academic Staff:</strong> means all persons holding appointments as members of the teaching and/or research staff, including professional Librarians of the University.</li>
                    <li><strong>Accelerated Promotion:</strong> means a promotion granted to an employee before he has spent three years\' maturation period on his salary scale.</li>
                    <li><strong>Academic Technologist:</strong> means all staff holding Lab teaching appointments in laboratories of various academic departments.</li>
                    <li><strong>Bursar:</strong> means the Bursar of the University.</li>
                    <li><strong>Child:</strong> means the biological child of an officer or a legally adopted child of an officer or the step child being the biological offspring of the spouse of the officer under 23 years of age and entirely dependent on the officer concerned.</li>
                    <li><strong>Centre:</strong> means any structural component of the University charged with specialized function established by Senate and approved by Council.</li>
                    <li><strong>College:</strong> means the College as constituted and established by the Senate and Council of the University.</li>
                    <li><strong>Council:</strong> means the Governing Council of the University.</li>
                    <li><strong>Criminal Offence:</strong> means stealing, false pretense, extortion forgery, official corruption, and such kind of offence involving moral turpitude in the Criminal Code of Nigeria and as may from time to time be defined in any criminal or penal code in force in any part of the Federation of Nigeria.</li>
                    <li><strong>Confirmed Employee:</strong> means an employee whose appointment has been confirmed by Council.</li>
                    <li><strong>Cognate Experience:</strong> means experience in University Administration or similar/relevant organization.</li>
                    <li><strong>Date of Appointment:</strong> means the date on which an employee assumed duty with the University.</li>
                    <li><strong>Department:</strong> means any component of the University academic or non–academic recognized by Senate and Council as an integral part of the University.</li>
                    <li><strong>Deputy Vice-Chancellor:</strong> means the Deputy Vice-Chancellor of the University.</li>
                    <li><strong>Director:</strong> means a member of staff who is appointed as Director of a Centre of the University in accordance with regulations or procedure for the time being in force.</li>
                    <li><strong>Faculty:</strong> means a Faculty as constituted and established by the Senate and Council of the University under the Lagos State University Law.</li>
                    <li><strong>Dean:</strong> means a member of staff who is appointed, elected or designated as the Dean of a Faculty of the University in accordance with regulations or procedure for the time being in force.</li>
                    <li><strong>Financial Year:</strong> means the period of twelve (12) months, which begins 1st January and ends 31st December.</li>
                    <li><strong>Family:</strong> means a relation to an Officer, Spouse with Children up to a maximum of four or in respect of an unmarried Officer, her Children up to a maximum of four, who are under the age of 23 years and are entirely dependent on the Officer.</li>
                    <li><strong>Graduate Assistant/Research Assistant:</strong> is a person engaged as Teaching Assistant/Research Assistant with the privilege to complete his Master Degree within two [2] years and get his appointment regularized.</li>
                    <li><strong>Head of Department:</strong> means a member of staff who is appointed as Head of Department of the University in accordance with regulations or procedure for the time being in force.</li>
                    <li><strong>Head of Unit:</strong> means a member of staff who is appointed as Head of Unit of the University in accordance with regulations or procedure for the time being in force.</li>
                    <li><strong>Incremental date:</strong> shall be October 1st of every year.</li>
                    <li><strong>Leave Year:</strong> means the period from 1st January of a given year to 31st December of the same year. The annual leave should be taken and exhausted within this period.</li>
                    <li><strong>Member of staff or Staff member:</strong> means an employee on permanent employment of the University holding an appointment as may be decided by Council from time to time.</li>
                    <li><strong>Medical Practitioner:</strong> shall have the meaning given to it by the Medical and Dental Practitioners Act of 1963: Law of Nigeria. Gazette 1963 No. 9</li>
                    <li><strong>Misconduct:</strong> means any conduct, which is prejudicial to the good name and/or reputation of the University. Without prejudice to the generality of this definition, misconduct includes:</li>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Falsification of records;</li>
                        <li>Suppression of records;</li>
                        <li>Withholding of files;</li>
                        <li>Conviction on a criminal charge (other than a minor traffic or sanitary offense or the like);</li>
                        <li>Removal of documents from personal file or confidential file;</li>
                        <li>Absence from duty without leave;</li>
                        <li>False claims against University Officials;</li>
                        <li>Engaging in partisan political activities;</li>
                        <li>Bankruptcy/Serious financial embarrassment;</li>
                        <li>Unauthorized disclosure of official information, etc;</li>
                        <li>Bribery;</li>
                        <li>Corruption;</li>
                        <li>Embezzlement;</li>
                        <li>Misappropriation;</li>
                        <li>Violation of Oath of Secrecy;</li>
                        <li>Action prejudicial to the security of the University/State;</li>
                        <li>Advance fee fraud (Criminal Code 419);</li>
                        <li>Holding more than one full-time paid job;</li>
                        <li>Nepotism or any other form of preferential treatment;</li>
                        <li>Divided loyalty,</li>
                        <li>Sabotage;</li>
                        <li>Wilful damage to University/Public property;</li>
                        <li>Sexual harassment/Rape;</li>
                        <li>Fighting while on duty;</li>
                        <li>Membership of cult(s);</li>
                        <li>Failure to appear for promotion exercise without reasonable Cause;</li>
                        <li>Insubordination;</li>
                        <li>Malicious and false whistle blowing;</li>
                        <li>Involvement in Examination Malpractice;</li>
                        <li>Decoding of records;</li>
                        <li>Battery;</li>
                        <li>Assault; and</li>
                        <li>Any other serious act unbecoming of a Public Officer.</li>
                    </ul>
                    <p>The following are the prescribed sanctions which may be applied in accordance with the regulations:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Dismissal</li>
                        <li>Reduction in rank</li>
                        <li>Reduction in salary</li>
                        <li>Withholding/Deferment of increment</li>
                        <li>Surcharge</li>
                        <li>Reprimand</li>
                        <li>Suspension</li>
                        <li>Termination of Appointment</li>
                        <li>Compulsory retirement</li>
                        <li>Suspension of increment</li>
                    </ul>
                    <li><strong>Non-Academic Staff:</strong> means all persons holding appointment other than enumerated in section (i) above.</li>
                    <li><strong>Officer:</strong> means any person employed by the University as a senior member of staff.</li>
                    <li><strong>Provost:</strong> means a member of staff who is appointed, elected or designated as a Provost of the College of the University in accordance with regulations or procedure for the time being in force.</li>
                    <li><strong>Promotion:</strong> means Elevation to the next higher salary grade based on merit and Performance. All promotions take effect from 1st of October of the year for which the promotion is due. No promotion shall become effective until it has been approved and determined by Council.</li>
                    <li><strong>Permanent Employee:</strong> means an employee whose appointment has been approved by Council or the Court of Governor of the Lagos State University College of Medicine in respect of all Senior Staff.</li>
                    <li><strong>Registrar:</strong> means the Registrar of the University.</li>
                    <li><strong>Regrading:</strong> means a salary adjustment with reference to an employee\'s qualification, experience, and ability. It may be utilized to overcome any previous anomaly in appointment but shall not be regarded as promotion.</li>
                    <li><strong>Recognized Body:</strong> means a body with legal fiat as defined by the Federal Government and accepted by the Governing Council.</li>
                    <li><strong>Public Service:</strong> means any service or employment recognized as such from time to time by the Constitution.</li>
                    <li><strong>School:</strong> means the School as constituted and established by the Senate and Council of the University</li>
                    <li><strong>Senior Staff:</strong> means a member of staff holding a Permanent and Pensionable appointment on CONUNASS 06/CONUATSS 07/CONUASS 01 and above or its equivalent and any other salary scale that may be approved from time to time.</li>
                    <li><strong>Senate:</strong> means the Senate of the University.</li>
                    <li><strong>Session or academic year:</strong> means the period of twelve months, which begins on 1st October and ends on 30th September of the following year unless otherwise fixed by an Act of Senate.</li>
                    <li><strong>Semester:</strong> means the half of an academic year containing (16) weeks</li>
                    <li><strong>Secretary:</strong> means the Secretary of a constituent College such as an Institute or School of the University.</li>
                    <li><strong>Temporary Appointee:</strong> means an employee who is not on permanent appointment for not more than a period of one year, within which the appointment must be regularized. Graduate Assistants/Research Assistants have up to two [2] years to obtain their Master Degree and be regularized.</li>
                    <li><strong>Transfer Value:</strong> means that amount paid and accepted in complete discharge of pension liability in respect of an employee at the time of his transfer to or from a public service.</li>
                    <li><strong>Terminal Salary:</strong> means the basic salary including all forms of allowances being paid to the employee at the date of his retirement.</li>
                    <li><strong>Transfer of Service:</strong> means the permanent release of an employee or an officer from one public establishment to another to enable him/her continue his/her service under the new establishment subject to mutual agreement between the two establishments that his/her service under the new employer would be continuous with his/her service with the former employer.</li>
                    <li><strong>Unit:</strong> means any component of the University academic or non–academic recognized by Senate and Council as an integral part of the University.</li>
                    <li><strong>University Librarian:</strong> means the Librarian of the University.</li>
                    <li><strong>University:</strong> means Lagos State University as established by the Lagos State University Law of 1983.</li>
                    <li><strong>Vice-Chancellor:</strong> means the Vice-Chancellor of the University.</li>
                    <li><strong>Visiting Scholar/Researcher/Fellow/Lecturer/Professor:</strong> is a Scholar from an institution who visits a host University and is projected to teach, lecture or perform research on a topic the visitor is valued for.</li>
                </ol>

                <h3>OFFICIAL ABBREVIATIONS</h3>
                <p>Abbreviation commonly used in official correspondence, but rarely in communication with the general public including the following:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>a.b.c - "at back cover"</li>
                    <li>a/c - "account"</li>
                    <li>Ag - "Acting"</li>
                    <li>A.I.E. - "Authority to Incur Expenditure"</li>
                    <li>a.y.c - "at your convenience"</li>
                    <li>b.c - "back cover"</li>
                    <li>B/F - "Brought forward"</li>
                    <li>b.o.f. - "back of file"</li>
                    <li>B.U. - "Bring Up: Brought Up"</li>
                    <li>B.U.F - "Bring Up File"</li>
                    <li>C.C. - "Carbon Copy"</li>
                    <li>C/F - "Carried forward"</li>
                    <li>Cap - "Chapter (usually of the Laws)"</li>
                    <li>c/o - "Care of"</li>
                    <li>Conf - "Confidential"</li>
                    <li>Cons - "Consideration"</li>
                    <li>Cont’d - "Continued"</li>
                    <li>D. - "Director"</li>
                    <li>D.A.V. - "Department Adjustment Voucher"</li>
                    <li>d/d - "Dated"</li>
                    <li>D.D - "Deputy Director"</li>
                    <li>Dept - "Department"</li>
                    <li>D/o - "Demi official (letter)"</li>
                    <li>D.V.E.A. Book - "Department Vote Expenditure Account Book"</li>
                    <li>e.g. - "for example"</li>
                    <li>Enc. - "Enclosure"</li>
                    <li>E.T.A. - "Estimated Time of Arrival"</li>
                    <li>etc. - "and so on"</li>
                    <li>E.T.D. - "Estimated Time of Departure"</li>
                    <li>F.&amp;P.A - "File and Put Away"</li>
                    <li>f.f.a. - "for further action"</li>
                    <li>f.i.o. - "for information only"</li>
                    <li>f.n.a - "for necessary action"</li>
                    <li>F.R. - "Financial Regulations"</li>
                    <li>f.y.c. - "for your consideration"</li>
                    <li>f.y.i. - "for your information"</li>
                    <li>H.E - "His Excellency"</li>
                    <li>H.O.D - "Head of Department"</li>
                    <li>H.O.C.S.F - "Head of Civil Service of the Federation"</li>
                    <li>Hon. - "Honourable"</li>
                    <li>Hqrts. - "Headquarters"</li>
                    <li>h/y - "herewith"</li>
                    <li>i/c - "in charge of"</li>
                    <li>i.d.c. - "in due course"</li>
                    <li>i.e (ID/EST) - "That is, in other words"</li>
                    <li>i.f.o. - "in favour of"</li>
                    <li>k.i.v. - "keep in view"</li>
                    <li>L.G - "Local Government"</li>
                    <li>L.P.C. - "Last Pay Certificate"</li>
                    <li>L.P.O - "Local Purchase Order"</li>
                    <li>Misc - "Miscellaneous"</li>
                    <li>n.a. - "not applicable (or necessary action)"</li>
                    <li>n.a.t - "necessary action taken"</li>
                    <li>N.B - "Nota Bene (take notice)"</li>
                    <li>n.f.a - "no further action"</li>
                    <li>O/C - "Office-in-charge"</li>
                    <li>O.K - "all correct"</li>
                    <li>P.A - "Put Away/Personal Assistant"</li>
                    <li>Para - "paragraph"</li>
                    <li>Perm. Sec - "Permanent Secretary"</li>
                    <li>P.S - "postscript: i.e. written afterwards"</li>
                    <li>pp (or pp) - "pages, papers"</li>
                    <li>P.T.O. - "Please Turn Over"</li>
                    <li>P.U. - "Put Up (papers of suggestion to an official)"</li>
                    <li>P.V - "Payment Voucher"</li>
                    <li>q.e.d. - "which was to be demonstrated"</li>
                    <li>recd - "received"</li>
                    <li>Re. - "Reference"</li>
                    <li>RSVP - "Respondez S\’il Vous Plait (Reply if you please)"</li>
                    <li>R.V - "Receipt Voucher"</li>
                    <li>Sec - "Secretary (or Section)"</li>
                    <li>s.f.c - "submitted for consideration"</li>
                    <li>s.f.i - "submitted for information"</li>
                    <li>s.f.s - "submitted for signature"</li>
                    <li>S.G.F. - "Secretary to the Government of the Federation"</li>
                    <li>S.I.V - "Stores Issue Voucher"</li>
                    <li>S.R.V - "Stores Receipt Voucher"</li>
                    <li>“T’’ - "Temporary"</li>
                    <li>T/y or T.y - "Thank you"</li>
                    <li>u.f.s - "under flying seal (to pass through a higher authority)"</li>
                    <li>w.r.t. - "With reference to"</li>
                    <li>your let - "Your Letter"</li>
                </ul>
            </body>

        ]]>
    </string>

</resources>